谢谢你们请我们过来
Thank you guys for having us over.
- 夫妻之夜真有趣    - 我们之前怎么会
- Yeah, this is fun, couples night.     - I don't know why we don't hang out...
- 不常和已婚的朋友聚餐？ - 因为每次…
-...with married couples more often.     - Because every time we do...
你都说荡秋千的笑话把他们吓走
...you make jokes about swinging and scare them away.
你说那对葡萄牙夫妻？换做是你也会这么做
You mean that Portuguese couple? Yeah, like you wouldn't have done it.
嘿 各位 我有好消息
Hey, you guys, I have great news.
- 罗斯…我们正在吃晚餐   - 我已经吃过了 但好吧
- Ross, we're kind of in the middle of dinner.     - Oh, well, I already ate, but sure.
- 你们猜我今天工作发生什么事？ - 一只恐龙在一百万年前死了？
- Guess what happened at work today.     - A dinosaur died a million years ago?
是六千五百万年 然后请你…
Uh, try 65 million years ago. And then try: Shh!
我的终生职评估表出来了 听说情况很乐观
My tenure review board met today, and I hear it's looking really good.
- 哇哦   - 耶
- Wow.     - Yeah.
你们知道 这在学术界意味着什么吗？
Do you have any idea what this means in academic circles?
我的生活有"搞头"了
I am gonna get laid.
- 你们好   - 你好
- Hi, you guys.     - Hey.
意大利菜
Oh, Italian.
有谁…有谁要再吃多一点吗？
No one... No one wanted seconds, right?
我不用了
No, I'm good.
各位 你们绝不会相信 有个人力仲介来电找我
Guys, you're never gonna believe it. This headhunter called me.
明天我要去古驰面试 古驰竟然要我
I have a meeting tomorrow with Gucci. Gucci wants me.
- 我快得到终生职了   - 恭喜
- I'm up for tenure.     - Congratulations.
- 你也是 真是巧   - 哦
- You too. What are the odds?     - Oh...
你们猜怎么着？
Guess what.
我终于把牙缝里的种子挖出来了
I finally got that seed out of my teeth.
我真不知该替谁高兴
I don't know who I'm happiest for.
我知道 他已经努力一整天了
I do. He's been working on that all day.
(中央咖啡厅)
嘿 摩妮卡 你把姓改成 盖勒宾会很怪吗？
Hey, Mon, was it weird changing your name to Geller Bing?
不会 叫起来很温馨
No. No, it felt nice to acknowledge this.
- 要去哪里改？ - 就是…
- Where'd you go to do it?     - Um, the...
姓名局…
The Ministry of Names...
总着
...Bureau.
你没去改？
You never did it.
对不起 我只是还不想
I'm sorry. It's just the idea of...
正式成为宾家人
Of being an official Bing.
让我告诉你…
Hey, I will have you know that...
我骗谁啊？小孩跟你姓 让宾家绝后吧
Ah, who am I kidding? Let's call the kid Geller and let Bing die with me.
- 拿去   - 谢谢
- Here you go.     - Thanks.
甜心 你要我冠夫姓吗？
Honey, would you want me to take your name?
随便 你的名字决定权在你
Oh, it's up to you. It's your name. You've gotta live with it.
- 试试看 叫我汉尼根太太   - 汉尼根太太
- Let's see. Call me Mrs. Hannigan.     - Mrs. Hannigan?
你没看到我很忙吗？
What, can't you see I'm in the middle of something?
我喜欢
I like it.
- 你们好   - 你好 乔伊
- Hey, guys.     - Hey, Joe.
我们要去新房子办点事 你要来吗？
We got things to check out at the new house. You want to come?
- 不 谢谢   - 我们搬家你不高兴…
- No, thank you. - You're not happy about us moving...
可是你是唯一还没见过房子的人
...but you're the only one who hasn't seen the house.
对啊 跟我们去你就知道有多近了
You'll see how close it is to the city.
不 一点都不近 你们说在公证托管
No, it's not close. You said it was in escrow.
可是地图上都找不到
I couldn't even find that on the map.
乔伊 拜托 这对我们很重要
Joey, please come. It would mean so much to us.
好吧 你们是好友 我也希望表达支持
You know what? You are my friends. I want to be supportive.
- 我会跟你们去… 我要坐车头   - 可恶
- I will come with you. Shotgun.     - Damn it.
回头见 我们11点来接你
See you guys later. We'll pick you up at 11.
- 很高兴你要来   - 好
- So glad you're coming.     - All right.
- 真好 你表现得很成熟   - 什么？我去的原因
- Good for you. That was really mature.     - What? The only reason I'm going...
是让他们看清所有房子的缺点
...to their stupid new house is to point out everything wrong with it...
他们才不会搬走 我要逼他们留下来
...so they don't move. I'm gonna make them stay here.
你真是奇怪的成年人
You're a strange kind of grown-up.
乔伊 你不能逼别人做不想做的事
Joey, you can't make someone do something they don't want to do.
相信我 我一直想叫麦克 在床上做一些事…
Believe me. There's something I've been trying to get Mike to do in bed, and...
- 现在不要谈这个好吗？ - 好吧 老古板
- Whoa. Can we not talk about that now?     - All right. Prude.
听着 摩妮卡和钱德 真的很喜欢那栋房子
Look, Monica and Chandler really love this house.
你是无法说服他们留下的
You are not gonna talk them into staying here.
我最会说服别人了
Hey, I can convince people to do anything, you know?
说不定我可以说服麦克做那件事 是什么？
I bet I could even get Mike to do that thing. What is it'?
我才不要帮你做那档事
I am not gonna help you do that!
老天啊
Oh, my God.
你好 我要找古．驰的坎贝尔先生
Hi. Um, I'm here to see Mr. Campbell, with Gucci.
应该是以古驰的名义订位的
The reservation's probably under Gucci.
拼起来很像"古鸡" 很容易搞混
It's spelled like "gucky," which can be confusing.
坎贝尔先生还没到 让我先带你到他的坐位上
Mr. Campbell's not here yet. Let me show you to his table.
天啊 是我的老板 请帮我们换位子
Oh, my God. That's my boss. You have to seat us somewhere else.
很抱歉 坎贝尔先生习惯坐那里
I'm sorry, that's always Mr. Campbell's table.
我不能让我老板瞧见 我在应征新工作
But my boss cannot see me. I'm interviewing for another job.
- 我知道 "古鸡"的工作   - 嘘
- I know. With Gucky. - Shh!
- 瑞秋？ - 我来约会
- Rachel?     - I'm on a date.
那很好
That's great.
没错 单身母亲 事业家庭两头忙
Yeah, it is. Yeah, you know, it's tough. Single mom. Career.
还是得轻松一下
You gotta get out there.
- 你真是活力充沛    - 哦
- Well, you've got a good energy.     - Oh.
- 瑞秋？ - 是的 你好
- Rachel?     - Yes, hi.
- 詹姆斯坎贝尔   - 你好
- James Campbell.     - Hi.
- 不好意思   - 请坐
- Excuse us.     - Please.
好的
Okay.
噢
Oh.
他真帅
He's cute.
所以
So...
你的履历真是精彩
...your resume is quite impressive.
我的履历？
My, ha, ha... My résumé?
我的…线上个人资料 应该不算是履历
I wouldn't... I wouldn't call my online dating profile a résumé.
个人资料？不… 我是说你的求职履历表
Dating profile? No, I'm... I'm talking about the work résumé.
这年头大家怎么都忽然不唱歌了？
Whatever happened to just singing for no reason?
可能因为觉得很诡异
Maybe people found it weird.
- 可能   - 那么…
- Maybe.     - 80...
- 你为何想离开劳夫罗伦？ - 什么？
- Why do you want to leave Ralph Lauren?     - What?
- 我没有   - 没有
- I don't.     - You don't?
对 我喜欢那里的工作
No, I love... I love it there.
你不想离开 那吃这顿饭的意义何在？
Well, if you don't want to leave, why are we having this lunch?
那是我的老板
That is my boss.
什么？
What?
那是我的老板
That is my boss.
那是雨果伯斯？
That's Hugo Boss?
这里真阴沉 我在这工作一定会自杀
God, this place is so depressing. If I had to work here, I'd kill myself.
显然你还没下手
But you obviously haven't.
- 有何可效劳？ - 我想改姓名
- How can I help you?     - I need to change my name, please.
我要改名躲避法律制裁
See, I need to change it because I'm hiding from the law.
你真健谈
You're fun.
- 请填妥这张表格   - 我想问一下…
- You need to fill out this form.     - Okay. Well, just so I know...
我不太了解作业过程 我姓布非
I don't know how it works. My name is Buffay...
我先生姓汉尼根
...and my husband's name is Hannigan.
该改成"布非汉尼根" 还是"汉尼根布非"？
So is it supposed to be "Buffay-Hannigan" or "Hannigan-Buffay"?
- 想改什么就改什么   - 不能随我高兴
- It can be anything you want.     - Well, not anything.
没错 随你高兴
Yeah. Anything.
这下有得瞧了
Oh, this could take a while.
- 不要挡住别人   - 好
- Get out of my line.     - Okay.
- 你们好   - 你好 菲比
- Hey.     - Hey, Pheebs.
已经不是了 我今天改名了
Oh, not anymore. I changed it today.
- 抱歉 汉尼根太太   - 又错了
- Oh, I'm sorry, Mrs. Hannigan.     - Wrong again.
既然可以随心所欲地改名
Apparently, you can change it to anything.
所以我想 "这是发挥创意的好时机"
So I thought, "All right, here's an opportunity to be creative."
现在我是康苏拉香蕉吊床公主
So meet Princess Consuela Bananahammock.
你抢了我们小孩的名字
That's what we were gonna name the baby.
- 菲比   - 康苏拉公主
- Phoebe.     - Ah, Princess Consuela.
- 你真的把名字改成那样？ - 额
- You changed your name to that?     - Uh-huh.
现在起我们得叫你康苏拉公主？
Okay, so from now on, we have to call you Princess Consuela?
不 我的朋友要叫我薇拉莉
No, I'm gonna have my friends call me Valerie.
- 面试结果如何？ - 不太好
- Hey, how did the interview go?     - Ugh. Not good.
每次面试完我都有这种成觉 一定比你想像中好
I always feel that way after an interview I'll bet it went better than you think.
我没得到古．驰的工作 而且还被劳夫罗伦炒鱿鱼
Well, I didn't get the job at Gucci and I got fired from Ralph Lauren.
真的是很糟的一次面试
That is a bad interview.
你说什么？发生什么事？
What are you talking about? How did this happen?
我老板也在我面试的那家餐厅
My boss was at the same restaurant where I was having my interview...
过程全都被他听到了
...and he heard everything.
之后他要我去他办公室 说要将我辞退
Later, he calls me into his office and tells me he'll have to let me go...
因为我没有向心力
...because I'm not a team player.
我说"等等 我有"
And I said, "Wait a minute. Yes, I am."
然后我坐在那45分钟
And then I had to sit there for 45 minutes...
听他举例证明 结果证明我真的没有向心力
...while he proved that that, in fact, was true.
- 天啊 我很遗憾   - 天啊
- Oh, God, I'm so sorry.     - God.
你们好
H93'-
这是什么？
What...? What's this?
一瓶香槟 怎么会跑来这里？
Why, it's a bottle of champagne. Why is this here?
- 罗斯   - 我想是因为…
- Ross.    - I guess it's here...
我得到终生职了
...because I got tenure!
- 恭喜   - 恭喜
- Congratulations.    - Wow.
这是我职业生涯最美妙的一天
This is the single greatest day of my professional career.
- 阿甘 拿6个杯子来   - 6个？
- Gunther. Six glasses.     - Six?
- 你要让我加入？ - 我以为乔伊也在 5个就好
- You want me to join you?   - I thought Joey was here. Five is good.
我明天的咖啡会被吐痰
Wow, I'm gonna have a loogey in my coffee tomorrow.
喔 以色列香槟
Ooh. Israeli champagne.
还是香草口味
And it's vanilla.
我得到终生职 又不是中乐透
I got tenure. I didn't win the lottery.
瑞秋 你的结果如何？
Hey, Rach, so, uh, how did your thing go?
不错 不过几天后才知道结果
Oh, good. But I won't hear about that for a couple days.
你一定会得到的 我有预感
Oh, you know what, you're gonna get it. I can feel it.
真的？
Can yQu'_7
好啦 各位敬罗斯
All right, everybody, here's to Ross.
多年的辛苦终于闻花结果
And to years of hard work finally paying off.
但事业并非代表一切
And to knowing that your career doesn't mean everything.
但却也相当重要
But also knowing it means a lot.
更重要的是拥有圆满的人生
But more importantly, to full, well-rounded lives.
还是要以成功事业为中心
That center around work.
- 敬罗斯   - 敬罗斯
- To Ross.    - To Ross.
知道最棒的是什么吗？ 我永远都不会被炒鱿鱼
You know what the best part about this is? I can never be fired.
- 天啊   - 我说真的
- Oh, God.     - No, seriously.
我有终生的职业保障
I have job security for life.
我永远都不必担忧
You know? I mean, I never have to worry.
瞧瞧你有多替我高兴
Oh, look at you. Look how happy you are for me.
不是 我今天被炒鱿鱼了
[CRYING] No, it's not that. I got fired today.
而且也没得到另一份工作
And I didn't get the other job.
- 瑞秋 我很抱歉  - 噢
- Oh, my... Rach, I'm so sorry.    - Oh...
- 天啊 我真白痴   - 没关系 你又不知情
- Great, I feel like an idiot.     - No, it's okay. You didn't know.
至少事先警告一下吧
Little heads-up would've been nice.
威谢你又让我们来看房子
Thank you for letting us see the house again.
还有谢谢你解释 公证托管的意思
And thank you for explaining to us what "escrow" means.
虽然已经忘了 但还是谢谢你
I've already forgotten what you said, but thank you.
要待多久都行 看完了再通知我
Take as long as you want. Just let me know when you're through.
好 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
- 很高兴你愿意来   - 我也是 这里不错
- Aw, so glad you decided to come.     - Me, too. Yeah, this place is great.
我很替你们高兴 但希望你们喜欢霉菌
So happy for you guys. Although, you know, I hope you like fungus.
- 什么？ - 霉菌
- What?     - Fungus.
这里到处都是
Yeah. Place is full of it.
才没有 我们请人检查过 这袒很干净
No, it's not. We had an inspection and they didn't find anything.
那为何我双眼又涩 喉咙又痒？
Okay. Then I guess I have dry eyes and a scratchy throat for no reason.
也许是因为整路上你像只狗
Maybe it's because you hung your head out the window like a dog...
把头伸出车窗外
...the whole ride here.
也许吧
Maybe.
这里是客厅？好暗
So this is the living room, huh? It's pretty dark.
- 才不会   - 你开什么玩笑？
- No, it's not.     - Are you kidding?
我在角落都看到蝙蝠了
I think I just saw a bat in the corner.
你把头伸出车窗外时 没有撞到信箱吧？
When your head was hanging out the window, it didn't hit a mailbox, did it?
也许有
Maybe.
我只是觉得你们 可以找到更好的房子
Look, I just think you guys can do better than this house, you know?
任何一栋都比这间好
Or any other house for that matter.
乔伊
Oh, Joey.
我们知道你很难接受 可是…
We know you're having a hard time with this, but we...
- 我们很喜欢这里   - 好吧 既然那么喜欢
- We love it here.     - Fine! If you love this house so much...
那就住吧 希望你们会习惯这怪声
...you should live here. I hope you get used to that humming sound.
- 乔伊 我们知道是你发出来的   - 不…
- Joey, we know that's you.     - No...
不是我
...it's not.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 欢迎回来   - 我好想你
- Welcome back.     - I missed you.
- 我也是   - 最近如何？
- Oh, me too.     - So, what's new?
我不再是菲比布非了
Well, I am no longer Phoebe Buffay.
- 太好了 你改名了？ - 没错
- That's great. You changed your name?     - Yes, I did.
我是康苏拉香蕉吊床公主
Meet Princess Consuela Bananahammock.
- 你在开玩笑对吧？ - 没有
- You're kidding, right?     - Nope.
- 你真的改了   - 对
- You really did that?     - Yep.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
为什么？
Why?
为什么？很有趣 特殊 又没有人跟你同名
Why? It's fun. It's different. No one else has a name like it.
那我也要改名
Then I'm gonna change my name.
太好了 你要改成什么？
Great. Okay, what are you gonna change it to?
屎袋
Crap B39-
- 麦克屎袋？ - 不 没有麦可 只有屎袋
- Mike Crap Bag?     - No. No "Mike." No, just "Crap Bag."
姓袋 名屎
First name: Crap. Last name: Bag.
- 你是认真的？ - 当然是认真的
- You're not serious, right?    - Yeah, I'm serious.
很有趣 特殊 又没有人跟你同名
It's fun, it's different, and no one else has a name like that.
也好 你喜欢我就喜欢
Uh-huh. Well, then great. lfyouloveiLlloveiL
我很喜欢 我也爱你的名字 我爱康苏拉公主
I do love it. And I love your name. I love Princess Consuela.
我爱屎
And I love Crap.
哦
Oh.
- 你是谁？ - 你好 我是乔伊
- Who are you?     - Oh, hi. I'm Joey.
我的蠢朋友要买这间房子 你是谁？
My stupid friends are buying this house. Who are you?
我是麦金莉 我的蠢父母要卖掉这间房子
I'm Mackenzie. My stupid parents are selling this house.
我讨厌我的父母
I hate my parents.
我讨厌我的朋友
I hate my friends.
听好 一定有法子阻止他们
Look, there's gotta be a way that we can stop this from happening.
例如？
Like what?
对了 你跟我来 跟他们说房子闹鬼
Oh! Okay, you come with me and you tell them that the house is haunted.
你是8岁小孩吗？
What are you, 8?
- 不然你有什么妙计？ - 我想不出来 我才8岁
- Okay. Let's hear your great idea.     - I don't have any great ideas. I am 8.
一定有其他办法…
Ah, there's gotta be a way. I mean, you know...
要是摩妮卡和钱德搬家 菲比又嫁给麦克
...if Monica and Chandler move out here, and Phoebe's married to Mike...
就剩下我 罗斯和瑞秋 你知道这代表什么吗？
...that just leaves me and Ross and Rach. You know what I mean?
不知道
I really don't.
怎么办？我要失去我的朋友了
What am I gonna do? I feel like I'm losing my friends.
- 我父母说朋友可以再交   - 你说得真容易
- My parents say I'll make new friends.     - Yeah, sure, easy for you.
你还年轻 我已经人老珠黄了
You're young. Me? I'm set in my ways.
我妈说得对"弄种爱发牢骚"
This is what my mom was talking about. Whiners are wieners.
听着 你希望你的朋友幸福吧？
Look, you want your friends to be happy, right?
对…应该吧
Yeah. Yeah, I guess. Yeah.
如果搬来这会让他们幸福 你不也希望如此吗？
Well, if moving here is gonna make them happy, don't you want them to do it'?
也许吧
Yeah. Maybe.
那就要放手让他们走
Then you've gotta let them go.
我不想承认 可是…
Oh, I hate to admit it, but you're...
你也许说得对
You're probably right.
你怎么会这么聪明？
How'd you get to be so smart?
我看很多书
I read a lot.
我还以为我跟你很合
Just when I thought we could be friends.
瑞秋 我听说了 我很遗憾
Oh, hey, Rach. I just heard. I'm so sorry.
谢谢你…
Oh, thank you...
你还是不知道我的名字？
You still don't know my name, do you?
现在没必要知道了
Well, now I don't have to.
罗斯 你怎么那么慢？
Ross, what is taking you so long?
很抱歉 它并不适合快速偷带走
I'm sorry. It's almost as if this wasn't built for a quick getaway.
瑞秋？
Rachel?
马克？天啊
Mark? Oh, my God.
- 你过得如何？ - 很好 你应该还记得罗斯
- How have you been?     - Fantastic. You remember Ross.
- 当然   - 哦
- Sure. Sure.  - Oh.
带椅子干嘛？
What's with the chair?
搭地铁要找位子不容易…
Uh... You know, you can't always get a seat on the subway, so...
真聪明
Clever.
你好吗？
So how are you?
你正好遇上我落魄的日子
Oh. You're not catching me on my best day.
一箱办公用品 看起来不像升官
Yeah, a box full of your desk stuff doesn't say "big promotion."
的确 但也好 可以休息一阵子
No, but it's good. You know, I'm gonna take some time off...
- 做些公益活动   - 你确定？
-...and do charity work.    - Are you sure?
路易威登这里也许有空缺
We may have something at Louis Vuitton.
去他的公益活动 有什么工作？
Screw charity work. What do you got?
不如一起吃顿晚餐再谈？
Why don't we have dinner and talk?
- 太好了 我打给你   - 好
- Great. I'll call you.     - Okay.
- 很高兴再见到你   - 我有终生职
- Nice to see you again.     - Yeah. Yeah. I got tenure.
老天啊
Oh, my God.
看吧？我就说会有好事发生
See? I told you something good would come along.
他人看起来不错 我见过他吗？
And he seemed really nice. I've met him before?
罗斯 他是马克
Ross, that's Mark.
布鲁明岱尔百货公司的员工 你以前很爱吃他的醋
From Bloomingdale's? You were insanely jealous of him.
- 那个是马克？ - 对
- That is Mark?     - Yes.
- 我讨厌那家伙   - 哦…
- I hate that guy.     - Oh...
不行…你不能和他去吃饭
No, no, no. You cannot go to dinner with him.
- 什么？你不希望我找到工作吗？ - 他一定会给你工作
- What? You don't want me to get a job?     - Yeah, I'm sure he'll give you a job.
或许当他的"性爱秘书"
Maybe make you his "sex-cretary."
我说真的 我不信任那家伙好吗？
I'm serious. I just don't trust that guy, okay?
你知道吗 …等会再说 警卫来了
You know what...? Okay, let's talk about it later. There comes security.
我好喜欢这街道
Oh, I love this street.
这些树和广大的前院 还有真正的篱笆
The trees and the big front yards and the actual picket fences.
天啊 那两只狗正在炒饭
Man, those two dogs are going at it.
嘿
Hey
- 嘿 你到哪去了？ - 就四处走走
- Hey. Where you been?     - Oh, just, uh, you know, looking around.
你们知道吗？
But you know what?
这间房子很棒
This house is great.
真的？是什么让你改变心意？
Really? What changed your mind?
住这里的小女孩说的话 让我平静许多
The little girl who lives here made me feel better about the whole thing.
乔伊 住这的小女孩 30年前就死了
Joey? There was a little girl who lived here, but she died, like, 30 years ago.
什么？
What?
我耍你的
I'm just messing with you.
不好笑 你明知道我最怕小女孩鬼
That's not funny. You know I'm afraid of little-girl ghosts.
乔伊 既然你不嫌弃这房子 你想看你的房间吗？
Joey, now that you're okay with the house, do you want to go see your room?
什么？
What?
我有自己的房间？
I get my own room?
我们买房子当然会 准备乔伊专属的房间
You don't think we'd buy a house and not have a Joey room, do you?
天啊
Oh, my God.
可以放水族箱吗？还有性爱秋千？
Hey, can I have an aquarium? And a sex swing?
- 不行   - 为什么？我又不会弄脏水槽
- No.    - Why not? I'll keep the tank clean.
你先请 香蕉吊床太太
After you, Ms. Bananahammock.
谢谢 袋先生
Thank you, Mr. Bag.
你好 丽塔
Oh, hey!
- 嗨 丽塔   - 你好吗？
- Oh, hi, Rita.     - How are you?
很好 丽塔是我按摩的客户
Good. Oh, Rita's a massage client.
对
Yeah.
你不介绍我吗？
Why don't you introduce me?
- 丽塔 这位是我先生   - 哦
- Rita, this is my husband.    - Oh.
不说名字吗？
Why don't you tell her my name?
好 我会说…这是我先生 屎袋
Okay, I will. This is, uh... This is my husband, Crap Bag.
屎袋？
Crap Bag?
想成一袋屎会比较好记
If you need an easy way to remember it, just think of a bag of crap.
- 好 失陪   - 好的
- Okay. Excuse me.     - Yeah.
好吧 我明白了 你可以做回麦克汉尼根吗？
Ugh. Okay, fine, you made your point. Can you please just be Mike Hannigan again?
只要你做回菲比布非就好
Only if you'll be Phoebe Buffay.
叫布非汉尼根如何？
How about, um...? How about Buffay-Hannigan?
- 真的？ - 耶
- Really? - Yeah.
对 我是菲比布非汉尼根香蕉吊床
I'm Phoebe Buffay-Hannigan-Bananahammock.
你真的知道香蕉吊床是什么吗？
Do you even know what a banana hammock is?
这个字很俏皮
It's a funny word.
它是一种泳裤
It's a Speedo.
喔 真糟糕
Oh, crap.
- 嘿 瑞秋在这里吗？ - 没有
- Hey, is Rachel here?    - Nope.
她还在吃晚餐？
She's still at dinner?
- 应该是 她跟谁在- 起？ - 布鲁明岱尔百货公司
- I guess. Why, who's she with?    - That guy, Mark...
那个叫马克的家伙 她以为他只想帮忙
...from Bloomingdale's. She thinks he's just being nice to her.
但我知道他只想把她弄上床
But I know he really wants to sleep with her.
都已经7年前的事了
It's seven years ago.
我的时光机成功了
My time machine works.
我们今天在街上遇见他 他说他可以聘请她
We ran into him on the street today, and he said he might have a job for her.
我看他只想跟她上床
But I know he just wants to get into her pants.
就算他想要她又如何？ 她单身而且他又很师
So, what if he wants to sleep with her? I mean, she's single, and he's cute.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
拜托
Oh, please.
昨天坐地铁时 你的眼睛
Yesterday, on the subway, you couldn't stop staring...
完全离不开那个大波霸
...at that woman with the big breasts.
让我告诉你 我是在看小婴儿
For your information, I was staring at her baby.
我们就要为人父母了
We're about to be parents.
对不起
Oh, sorry.
- 你们好   - 你好
- Hi, you guys.     - Hi. So...
- 晚餐如何？ - 很棒 马克体贴
-...how was dinner?     - Oh, it was great. Mark is so sweet.
是吗？为什么？那个下三滥有何企图？
Oh, yeah? Yeah, I wonder why? What could that smarmy letch possibly want?
罗斯 够了 他的婚姻美满 老婆刚生了双胞胎
Oh, Ross. Come on. He is happily married. His wife just had twins.
我们该送礼吗？
Should we send something?
工作的事如何？
How did the job stuff go?
他要聘请我
He offered me one.
- 太好了   - 恭喜
- That's great.     - Congratulations.
我知道 太神奇了
I know, it's amazing.
工作比起以前在劳夫罗伦好太多了
It's amazing. It's so much better than what I had at Ralph Lauren.
- 薪水也很棒   - 等等…
- The money is great.     - Can we...?
先暂停一下 是谁说会有好事发生？
Can we just stop for a second? Who said something better would come along? Huh?
你还不信 我就说一切都会好转
You didn't believe me. I told you everything was gonna work out.
这该用以色列最高档香槟庆祝
You know what? This calls for a bottle of Israel's finest.
工作地点在巴黎
The job is in Paris.
虽然演肥皂剧是不错
I mean, this soap opera is a great gig...
可是好机会也擦身而过
...but am I missing opportunities?
我一直以严肃的演员自居
You know, I've always thought of myself as a serious actor.
我该多参与独立制片的电影吗？
Should I be trying to do more independent movies?
我不知道
I don't know.
不如这样 我让我的熊听
But you know what? I'm gonna put you on with my bear.
等等
Hold on.
熊哥 我需要你给我职业上的建官
Hey, Bailey, I need some career advice.